

GOWTHAM.B



SUMMARY

QUALITY ASSURANCE MANGER.

meticulous, detail-oriented professional with 12 years of experience in some of the reputed companies. Wide exposure in Process & Quality Control, Costing, Vendor Development, FACTORY AUDIT. Compliance and Client Relations. Thorough knowledge of knits. Excellent communication skills and Computer Savvy.



EXPERIENCE

1. Merchandiser at Primex Apparels Sourcing Services pvt ltd , APR-2011 –2013-JAN

Started the career at 2010 in this company, learned at lot of the industry practices.

2.Robe mall apparels Private Limited -Bangalore JAN-2013-2016-SEP SR.QUALITY ASSURANCE EXECUTIVE FOR TIRUPPUR.

A bang lore based retail and E com Menswear brand , Handling the their Tirupur operation for Knitwear Procurement. Handling the supplier audits for the New vendor development and Licensed Products.

3.INMARK RETAIL Pvt ltd, Bangalore. SR.Quality Assurance ASST QUALITY MANAGER, (SEP-2016 – 2019-MAY)

Bangalore based Retail and Export sourcing office. Handled their operations at tirupur and South Tamilnadu for the Active wear. Travelling to the allover India for the New vendor audits etc.,

4. Kontoor Brands India (Spin off company VF Corporation USA) MAY-2019 to Sep 2020 Senior Vendor Quality Assurance Officer

Handling Vendor Operations at vendor Base on South and North Regions .

Providing technical assistance to suppliers to made the better manufacturing practice

5. BUREAU VERITAS CONSUMER PRODUCT SERVICES INDIA., TIRUPPUR- OCT 2020 -JAN 2023.01.22

Senior Quality Inspector.

Inspection and Auditing service providing company, Posted at their office for the Inspection and tractability Auditing for the renowned international clients. Making the Report for the client portal train the vendors to adopt the New Updates and implements provided by the client. Experienced in the Client and Company PLM Software.

6. OVS INDIA SOUCRING PVT LTD., TIRUPUR - JAN-2023 TO NOV-2023. SENIOR QUALITY ASSURANCE EXECUTIVE .

Posted at Tirupur office for the Vendor follow up . handling the internal technical auditing with company tool , Monitoring the vendor performance for the Social and Ethical compliance audit performance . maintain the SQL & OQL For the Allotted Factory , Providing the technical assistance to the vendor for Better product . maintain the Integrity of the Product

EDUCATION

DGMFT completed with 97% Marks (Diplomain garment Merchandising & Fashion Technology.,) At Essar Institute Of Fashion Technology, Tiruppur .

BSC.CDF; MADURA COLLEGE OF ARTS AND SCIENCE IN MADURAI

HSC From Vk Govt Hr. Sec. School, Tirupur secured 45 %

SSLC From Bishop Ubaharasamy Hr. Sec. School, Tirupur secured 40%

Email:

gowthambaskar@hotmail.com

Phone: +91 9159576705

+916380628715

Address: 193 kg nagar 1st street srinagar post tirupur-641603